[
{
     "qno": 1,
"question": "She ___ to the market yesterday.",
"opa": "go",
"opb": "goes",
"opc": "went",
"opd": "going",
"correctanswer": "3"
},
{
     "qno": 2,
"question": "They ___ dinner when the phone rang.",
"opa": "had",
"opb": "were having",
"opc": "have",
"opd": "has",
"correctanswer": "2"
},
{
     "qno": 3,
"question": " I ___ my homework before the movie started.",
"opa": "finish",
"opb": "had finished",
"opc": "finished",
"opd": "was finishing",
"correctanswer": "2"
},
{
     "qno": 4,
"question": " He ___ TV all evening.",
"opa": "watch",
"opb": "watched",
"opc": "was watching",
"opd": "had watched",
"correctanswer": "3"
},
{
     "qno": 5,
"question": "We ___ in London for five years.",
"opa": "lived",
"opb": "live",
"opc": "were living",
"opd": "had been live",
"correctanswer": "1"
},
{
     "qno": 6,
"question": "The train ___ before we reached the station.",
"opa": "left",
"opb": "was leaving",
"opc": "had left",
"opd": "leaves",
"correctanswer": "3"
},
{
     "qno": 7,
"question": " I ___ a strange noise last night.",
"opa": "hear",
"opb": "heard",
"opc": "was hearing",
"opd": "had hear",
"correctanswer": "2"
},
{
     "qno": 8,
"question": "While she ___, it started to rain.",
"opa": "walked",
"opb": "was walking",
"opc": "has walked",
"opd": "walks",
"correctanswer": "2"
},
{
     "qno": 9,
"question": " They ___ the movie already when I arrived.",
"opa": "watched",
"opb": "had watched",
"opc": "were watching",
"opd": "watches",
"correctanswer": "2"
},
{
     "qno": 10,
"question": " They ___ the movie already when I arrived.",
"opa": "studies",
"opb": "studied",
"opc": "had studied",
"opd": "was studying",
"correctanswer": "4"
}
]

